<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Dipankar Sarkar</title><link>https://www.dipankar.name/</link><description>Recent content on Dipankar Sarkar</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.dipankar.name/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About</title><link>https://www.dipankar.name/about/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.dipankar.name/about/</guid><description>A seasoned leader in technology with a track record in blockchain, machine learning, and web-scale architecture. Demonstrated successes at Nykaa, Hike, and Boom Protocol. Well-respected in the field with numerous contributions to machine learning conferences and patents.</description></item><item><title>Contact</title><link>https://www.dipankar.name/contact/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.dipankar.name/contact/</guid><description>Dipankar is a seasoned digital business consultant with expertise in a wide range of tech domains. He provides services such as team building, product launching, early-stage fundraising, and tech scaling. With an impressive track record, he seeks meaningful collaborations and high impact roles in Product &amp;amp; Engineering. Dipankar is interested in solving intriguing technology problems and establishing research collaborations with innovative companies.</description></item><item><title>Industry</title><link>https://www.dipankar.name/industry/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.dipankar.name/industry/</guid><description>This is a detailed professional portfolio of an individual with more than 14 years in the tech industry. Their accomplishments span across driving multimillion-dollar businesses, scaling consulting operations, filing patents, and publishing machine learning research. The individual has a robust consulting history, working with top companies across India in different capacities. In addition, they have a substantial employment background in senior engineering roles. The individual&amp;rsquo;s experience is further broadened by their participation in numerous internships.</description></item><item><title>Research</title><link>https://www.dipankar.name/research/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.dipankar.name/research/</guid><description>D. Sarkar is a proficient researcher in machine learning, cryptography, and distributed systems, with numerous publications and patents to his name. With a book on Nginx web server under his belt, Sarkar&amp;rsquo;s research papers span across federated learning and continuous optimization. Sarkar holds a Masters from Arizona State University in Computer Science with a specialisation in Cyber-Security and a B.Tech from the Indian Institute of Technology. Notable achievements include being awarded for the best project at IIT Delhi&amp;rsquo;s Open House and an excellent academic performance by Eta Kappa Nu - the engineering honor society of IEEE.</description></item><item><title>Startups</title><link>https://www.dipankar.name/startups/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.dipankar.name/startups/</guid><description>Dipankar Sarkar has a history of launching and advising tech start-ups, with expertise in blockchain, machine learning, microblogging, and more.</description></item><item><title>Bharat ka Twitter</title><link>https://www.dipankar.name/writings/bharat-ka-twitter/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.dipankar.name/writings/bharat-ka-twitter/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Made with love in California&amp;rdquo; - Talk about a one-line growth hack. We had made it with love, but sitting in my co-founder&amp;rsquo;s room in Kalkaji, New Delhi. We were competing with the valley boys and how (2007-9)!</description></item></channel></rss>